Hay everybody she told formation Boss did you
know that English is a very widely spoken
language in India in fact
whenever we do the street interviews
yours always wonder that
why people are answering in
English and modern jewellery.
What do Indians think about this
actually aware of how their
actions sounds that had the
streets of Mumbai to find out
if you have to guess what
percentage of Indian population
can speak fluent English
Any
colleges of school lowest price in Hindi
at all with everything needed to English is
also I think that 70 to
80% might know English English is
far more important than Hindi write
for Indians
having
4245 person around people speak
fluent English I guess around
75% of Indian people can
speak English fluently.
Most
of them are from South India because they are like
they are much more educated
than the people living in North India
that my opinion and
my I am I film south ine. So
Indian English
does have a particular accent
do you agree with that?
I think it
does proper English
So it's not action is
proper English
any
problem with the people as such because
that is the way we talked
does normal write your experience
as an Indian
person. Who were you aware that foreigners
often makes fun of the Indian
English accent.
It is actually
or when I
have not personally and counted the
situation, but my
cousins who live in the US is
pleased that you need US
accent of English but still get
jaj
Indian and
why it's
basically racism and
its sense to me physically,
but I
went to night status
of this program English one
of their English search doesn't make any difference.
I think it
is better than the US because
they are I think they are like
Not that good looks exactly like
sorry. Sorry not
often. It looks like the spitting
and I think accent is better.
No, no,
I
think
They need to learn English from as
it is like when we are them we
find it funny
that
people understand I want to
say that only
characters like up from
the Simpsons have
perpetuated stereotype in western culture
that Indian sound funny when
they speak English how does that
make you feel I
think it's if
you watch if I think it's funny
at times, but then it really
annoys you will kill, you know, you
stereotyping as a little too much
you taking too far.
We don't really sound like
that over time by
ok you
guys to the foreigner
funny to anybody in
India because that is the way we talked
to people understand that
the main thing sometimes I feel
offended but the
exaggerated more I think
We don't speak like that
firstly, but I feel
offended sometime I
do
not like that stop doing dark
them to you which English accent
sounds funny or weird.
The way Russian speak
Amitabh people those who
have their languages Russian or
French
English
speaking people seriously. My brother
has been Australia and his action
is literally funny
for me. Australian accent
is I really don't understand any
of it literally enough
doesn't understand
the
wrong medical use. I
find Chinese English quite funny,
which is the they don't use
the proper in a grammatical
things.
So their
languages
pronounce
it very well that
everybody
speak English as opposed to the native
Indian languages in India IAS
beating in English is
a friend or maybe
it is like to show
off or something.
If you know English you have lots of
friends and I
will your pool
because
they want the kids to speak English so
that when the Goodwill School the don't
feel ashamed that every child
is taught from an early
young age
at
my home. I should speak now native language
and he pays good fees for my school
school the responsibility
to teach me English so how does
everyone was but that's our
water.
Most of the people
people feel that
when there are educated in
English they will have thyroid
job opportunities and then
their dream about going to
other countries for job
that the basic reason for them learn English
otherwise they would not even be interested in knowing the
language to speak fluent English
do people treat you better.
Yeh in India vs IST in
that
you
have
them
making
changes in speak English now.
Can I must be life who like
to talk to a girl
while you
are
talking in English and especially when you talking dinner
fluently
respect
the usually give to other people were talking in other
languages English is becoming a
dominant language in Indian society.
Are you have a concern that
traditional Indian languages might
disappear is
going on right now given
academic any today
jealousness start to
speak in English and write English
afraid of the right now because
We bring you the of India we shall
take care of this thing that we should not
forget our own native language if this continues
for that day is
not far that this
this will be our national
not quite
concerned about it because we
often have many organisations and
cultural committee is to focus on
other languages. So I don't think it is
dying out because there are many people who
supported and I want our
traditional languages to last forever.
I am I am bit concerned because
as I said before
it is life when a child is
born, they are taught English
fast and then the mother tongue or
not at all a good
thing for me even now
we are speaking about English Vinay
discussing any other language
that
itself
shows how we give
English more important than any other
disappear
the regional languages. What would that mean for the
next generation of Indians Goa
It would be
really bad. I think people
from other countries come to India
to see the culture and
everything and we might just lose it
on the way. I
just hope we don't really
think it would
go anywhere
continue speaking Hindi
Marathi anything learn to speak
language language is important. But
do not forget you come from society
group of people of
different committee. Do not forget that
do not forget your roots
English
language
in your country. And how is it
affecting your community is
sure to subscribe to Asian
Boss for more insight into the
latest news and cultural
Trends all over Asia
thanks everybody. See you next
time.